We're going to prove today that the same pants looks good on different body types
and for that I have back up here this is Kiki. Hi everyone! And we have the new
Paradise collection, the Jungle Fantasy collection. This is a special video
because she's never been here on my channel. Welcome! Thank you! And grab your
pants so we can start. Kiki you have the black ones, the black Pantr and I have
different colors here I have blue and red and green and beige but I'm going to
try on blue I guess. I think blue because of the hair. As always. Then I would need pink.
Yeah, no pink available. I'll show you my secret how to dress paradise pants really fast.
okay one two three and well that didn't work try again you're gonna spend a bit
better just do it like this one two three yay Wow
Wow! It worked! Finally! Well done!
Let's turn around.
Oh and I need shoes because somehow you wear shoes and I don't.
Yeah, it's better than me.
Alright, now I'm taller.
Yeah.
So we have different sizes.
Yeah. Okay.
So you're wearing size...
Large. And I'm wearing size small.
It's the same pattern, the same lip part.
The other day I said Leo print because Leo is the total German pronunciation of Leopard.
So I don't know.
Looks really good.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I thought that I was gonna be part of this video.
No, sorry, not today.
Today I don't have a video for you.
I mean, you could join.
No, no hands don't want anymore.
Fuzz?
Well, let's try.
Which one? I don't know.
Which one do you want?
Red or this?
You want the blue one.
You want the blue one?
Or green?
I would say this.
The red one?
Yep.
Match it to the hair.
What have to do? You can show me guys. I can show you. You have to do the pants on the side.
You have to shake it and I'm holding until three. One, two, three. I can put it here. Right?
Well. Understand? Shake it. One, two, three.
Yay! Look! Natural. It fits perfectly with my hair color.
Yeah. It's super soft. I really like it. Oh well.
Okay, so we have three colors out of five. Basically half the collection. Even more.
And what was the point in the beginning of the video? To prove that the parents look
good on like every kind of body? And every hair color. And every hair color.
And I think... Let's turn around again.
I don't know, you can tell us in the comments what do you think. I think it was pretty good.
Yeah, I think so too.
Also the combination with the boots and the top is nice. We don't have shoes, so it doesn't count.
I have to say I love the pattern. When I first tried on the black one I thought, animal prank.
I love animal print.
But it's cool.
So how would you style it?
With the casual black top I guess.
Or like some leather thingies maybe?
Yeah, leather thingies.
Like a jacket.
Like a jacket or a top or a bra with some mesh on it.
A bra with mesh?
With a mesh top?
With a mesh top.
How innovative.
I think blue would look good on you too.
I think with the hair.
Because of my pin hair?
Maybe, but I've seen you in my Celine Knox Paradise pants so I know that blue looks good
on you.
Anyway, I think we're going to have some pizza too now.
Yeah, I think too.
Yeah.
So now I'm going to show you my trick.
Oh wow.
Me too.
Well, thanks for watching guys! Leave a thumbs up, subscribe to my channel, check out Kiki's
and Fuxi's socials, I will link them below the video. And we're going to have pizza now.
Bon appetit! See you next time! Bye!